Guide to the Robert Earl Cushman Papers, 1915; 1941-1988 UA.29.02.0159
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
Robert Earl Cushman Papers
1915, 1941-1988
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
Cushman, Robert Earl
UA.29.02.0159
25 Linear Feet
Robert Earl Cushman was a professor of systematic theology at Duke University, and was dean of the Divinity School from 1958-1971. He was involved internationally in issues related to the Methodist Church, ecumenism, and theological education. This collection contains correspondence, photographs, press clippings, meeting minutes and agendas, sermons, lectures, articles, publications, and other materials documenting his work within Duke Divinity School as well as his interactions with scholars and religious leaders worldwide. Files include records about internal business, courses, recruitment outreach, and student activism at Duke Divinity School; records about Cushman’s activities with the Association of Methodist Theological Schools, the World Council of Churches, and the Second Vatican Council of the Roman Catholic Church, where he was a Methodist observer during 1963-1965; writings, lectures and sermons; and personal materials.
Arrangement
This series is arranged into four series: Duke University Administrative Materials, Professional Activities, Writings, and Personal Materials.
Biographical / Historical
Robert Earl Cushman was born December 26, 1913, in Fall River, Mass. His father, Ralph, was a Methodist pastor and bishop. Robert Cushman graduated with his A.B. from Wesleyan University in Middletown, Conn., in 1936; was ordained a Methodist minister, and received his doctorate from Yale University in 1942. He taught theology at Yale and the University of Oregon before joining the faculty of Duke Divinity School in 1945 as a professor of systematic theology. Cushman was appointed dean of the Divinity School in 1958 by Duke President Hollis Edens, succeeding former Divinity School Dean James Cannon. Cushman’s tenure as dean (1958-1971) included a physical expansion of the Divinity School as well as an intensive self-study of the school’s admission policies and course curriculum. He participated in the 1968 prayer service at Duke after the assassination of Martin Luther King, Jr., and examined how other social issues, including the Vietnam war, race relations, and the “hippie” movement, affected the values and behavior of incoming divinity students.
Cushman was involved internationally in issues related to the Methodist Church, ecumenism, and theological education. He was a Methodist observer at three sessions of the Second Vatican Council of the Catholic Church, in 1963, 1964, and 1965. Throughout his term as dean and in his professional life, he continually stressed the importance of a solid theological education for those being trained for the ministry. He took part in visitations of other theological schools; served on the General Conference of the Methodist Church and the World Council of Churches; and was involved in establishing The Ecumenical Institute for Advanced Theological Studies in Tantur, near Jerusalem, which saw its first scholars take residence in 1971. The institute grew out of the ecumenical associations formed between Catholic, Protestant, and Orthodox Christians at the Second Vatican Council (Vatican II). Cushman also lectured widely and published numerous articles, including the James A. Gray lectures on the Second Vatican Council (with Fr. Godfrey Leo Diekmann); co-edited a volume of essays in honor of theologian Robert Lowry Calhoun (Harper & Row, 1965); and published the book Faith Seeking Understanding: Essays Theological and Critical with Duke University Press (1981). In the 1960s and 1970s, he was an editor with the Wesley Works project with Oxford University Press, which was aimed at producing a comprehensive set of volumes on the works of John Wesley.
After a sabbatical following his resignation as dean, Cushman returned to full-time teaching in 1972 and retired in 1979, dividing his time between Durham and Maine. In 1980, the Robert E. Cushman Chair of Christian Theology was established at Duke Divinity School. In the early 1980s, Cushman continued to write, correspond with former students and colleagues, teach distance courses, and direct graduate students. He also took up painting, and preached memorial services for several friends, including Duke theology professor H. Shelton Smith and other former divinity school faculty members. Cushman died on June 8, 1993. He and his wife Barbara had three children, Robert Earl Cushman, Jr., Thomas, and Elizabeth.
Access Restrictions
Records, such as search committee files or others pertaining to employment where individuals are identified, are closed for 70 years.
In accordance with the Family Education Rights and Privacy Act of 1974 as amended, Duke University permits students to inspect their education records and limits the disclosure of personally identifiable information from education records.
Use of audio materials from this collection requires the creation of reference copies. Reference copies for some materials may have been made, and if a reference copy exists, it is noted in this finding aid. To arrange for the creation of reference copies of other items, please contact University Archives staff. Although these recordings are now stored in a stable environment, their condition and playback quality is unknown.
Researchers must register and agree to copyright and privacy laws before using this collection.
All or portions of this collection may be housed off-site in Duke University's Library Service Center. The library may require up to 48 hours to retrieve these materials for research use.
Please contact Research Services staff before visiting the University Archives to use this collection.
Related Materials
Divinity School Records, Duke University Archives, David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library, Duke University.
Scope and Contents
This collection documents the administrative, professional, and personal activities of Robert Earl Cushman, who was dean of the Duke Divinity School from 1958-1971. The collection is organized into four series. Series, subseries and file names are based on the creator’s original folder labels and groupings of material. Duke University administrative materials focus on the business of the divinity school, including Cushman’s correspondence with faculty, students and administration; school committee reports; clippings; and materials related to the curriculum, student admissions and student activism. Professional materials include correspondence with church leaders and with the heads of theological schools; the series also includes reports, bulletins, clippings, and correspondence documenting Methodist conferences and ecumenical activities in which Cushman participated, both in the United States and abroad, such as his experience in Rome during the Second Vatican Council. The writings series contains drafts and final copies of lectures, articles, and sermons; a bound copy of Cushman’s doctoral dissertation; files related to the Wesley Works project; bound copy of his doctoral dissertation about Plato and some clippings and research materials. Personal materials contains correspondence with family, friends, and colleagues; as well as memorabilia, clippings, and miscellaneous documents, including one 1915 document from World War I. The collection contains photographs; an oversize blueprint of the proposed Divinity School renovation; and a recording of an address by King Hussein of Jordan.
Ecumenical movement; Education (Christian theology); Methodist Church -- United States; Duke University. Divinity School; World Council of Churches; Vatican Council (2nd: 1962-1965: Basilica di San Pietro in Vaticano)
- Duke University Administrative Materials, 1944-1986; 1
  Scope and Contents
  Materials here include correspondence with central Duke administration, students, faculty, and alumni of the Divinity School; minutes and agendas from committee meetings; materials on a major review of the Divinity School curriculum conducted in the late 1960s; an internal Divinity School self-study conducted in 1970; and various files on student activism in the 1960s and 1970s. The series is arranged into four subseries: Correspondence: Central University Administration; Correspondence: Divinity School Business, Students and Faculty; Divinity School Committees and Operations; and Student Dissent.
  - Correspondence: Central University Administration, 1950-1984; 1
    Correspondents represented in this series include Duke President Hollis Edens and other Duke administrators. This subseries is filed alphabetically by correspondent last name or subject of the correspondence.
    - John O. Blackburn, 1970-1971 (Box 1)
    - Taylor Cole, 1960-1970 (Box 1)
      Conditions Governing Access
      Restricted until 2040
    - Dozier, John: Business, 1961-1966 (Box 1)
    - Edens, Hollis A., 1950-1968 (Box 1)
    - Edens, Hollis A., 1953-1954 (Box 1)
    - Edens, Hollis A., 1955-1956 (Box 1)
    - Edens, Hollis A., 1957-1958 (Box 1)
    - Edens, Hollis A., 1959-1960 (Box 1)
    - President Edens Reports, 1958-1960 (Box 1)
    - Edens, Dr. Hollis A., 1963-1964 (Box 1)
    - Edens' Resignation: Newspaper Clippings, 1960 (Box 1)
    - Edens' Successor, 1960-1962 (Box 1)
    - deVyver, Dr. Frank T., 1963-1969 (Box 1)
    - Vice-President Gross, 1950-1965 (Box 1)
    - Hallowell, John H.: Department of Political Science, 1968-1969 (Box 1)
    - Herring, Herbert J., Vice-President, 1960-1965 (Box 1)
    - Langford, Thomas A., 1959-1970 (Box 1)
    - The Provost Affair, 1960 (Box 1)
    - Hart, Deryl, 1961-1964 (Box 1)
    - Hobbs, Marcus, 1968-1970 (Box 1)
    - Hobbs, Marcus, 1959-1963 (Box 1)
    - Hobbs, Marcus E., 1970 (Box 1)
    - Jordan, Charles E., 1966 (Box 1)
    - President Knight: Conversations, 1964-1965 (Box 1)
    - Knight, Douglas M., 1968-1969 (Box 1)
    - Knight, Dr. Douglas Maitland 1, 1962-1965 (Box 1)
    - Knight, Dr. Douglas Maitland 2, 1966-1969 (Box 1)
    - Latty, Dean E. R., 1965 (Box 1)
    - Dr. Harold Lewis, 1969-1971 (Box 1)
      Restricted until 2041
    - President Terry Sanford, 1970-1984 (Box 1)
    - President Terry Sanford, 1969-1971 (Box 1)
    - Womble, B. S.: Chairman of the Board of Trustees, 1961-1963 (Box 1)
  - Correspondence: Divinity School Business, Students, and Faculty, 1944-1986; 2
    Letters and memos between Divinity Dchool faculty members, between Cushman and students, or about particular topics relating to the Divinity School. Some have to do with Cushman’s hiring, resignation from the deanship, and retirement from Duke. Correspondents in this subseries include Dean James Cannon and Dean Thomas Langford, Cushman’s successor. This subseries is filed alphabetically by correspondent last name or subject of the correspondence.
    - A, 1961-1965 (Box 1)
    - Alumni: Overseas Correspondence, 1963-1965 (Box 1)
    - Alumni: Correspondence, 1960-1967 (Box 1)
    - Alumni: Bequests and Funds, 1959-1963 (Box 1)
    - Alumni Meeting: Baltimore Conference, 1966 (Box 1)
    - B, 1958-1965 (Box 2)
    - Brinkley, Dr. William L., 1963-1967 (Box 2)
    - Brower, A. S., 1961, 1964 (Box 2)
    - Book List, 1961-1965 (Box 2)
    - C, 1961-1965 (Box 2)
    - Campbell, Dennis M., Dean, 1983-1984 (Box 2)
    - Cornell College, 1959-1962 (Box 2)
    - Convocation, 1982 (Box 2)
    - Cushman, Robert E. (begin Employment), 1944-1954 (Box 2)
    - Cushman, Robert E., 1949-1957 (Box 2)
    - Cushman, Robert E., 1950-1956 (Box 2)
    - Cushman, Robert E.: REC Chair of Christian Theology, 1980 (Box 2)
    - D, 1959-1965 (Box 2)
    - Duodecim, 1964-1971 (Box 2)
    - E, 1962-1965 (Box 2)
    - Ehlhardt, Rev. Georgre (James Cannon Letter), 1961 (Box 2)
    - F, 1961-1965 (Box 2)
    - Faculty Correspondence, 1968 (Box 2)
    - Faculty Correspondence, 1975 (Box 2)
    - Ferrum Junior College, 1959-1964 (Box 2)
    - Finch, George Scholarship, 1959-1961 (Box 2)
    - The Frank Baker Library, 1960-1961 (Box 2)
    - G, 1959-1965 (Box 2)
    - Graduate Students - Current Business, 1972-1980 (Box 2)
      Restricted until 2050
    - H, 1959-1965 (Box 2)
    - Hickman, Veva (Mrs. Frank S.), 1973-1974 (Box 2)
    - I, 1961-1977 (Box 2)
    - Ingram, Kelly - Langford Course on Methodism, 1980 (Box 2)
    - Inaugural and Dedication File, 1963-1965 (Box 2)
    - J, 1959-1965 (Box 2)
    - Jones, President Jas. A., 1962 (Box 2)
    - K, 1960-1965 (Box 2)
    - L, 1962-1965 (Box 2)
    - Langford, Thomas, 1962-1980 (Box 2)
    - Mc, 1962-1964 (Box 2)
    - M, 1959-1965 (Box 2)
    - N, 1960-1965 (Box 2)
    - Nelson, Fletcher - Divinity School Development, 1968-1970 (Box 2)
    - O, 1959-1965 (Box 2)
    - Orientation Program, 1965 September 18 (Box 2)
    - Orientation Program, 1960-1965 (Box 2)
    - Orientation - Communication to Entering Juniors, 1963-1965 (Box 2)
    - P, 1961-1965 (Box 3)
    - Petry, Ray C., 1949-1957 (Box 3)
    - Divinity School Faculty - Correspondence etc., 1952-1957 (Box 3)
    - Petry, Ray C., 1972-1976 (Box 3)
    - Price, Irene, 1962-1963 (Box 3)
    - Q, 1959 (Box 3)
    - R, 1961-1965 (Box 3)
    - Ramsey, P., 1972-1988 (Box 3)
    - Recruitment Committee (ad hoc), 1965 (Box 3)
    - Recruitment, 1961-1966 (Box 3)
    - Remedial English (Ludington), 1963-1966 (Box 3)
    - Richey, McMurry S., 1972-1984 (Box 3)
    - Resignation, 1970 (Box 3)
    - REC Resignation and Data, 1970 (Box 3)
    - REC Resignation - Response andCorrespondence, 1970-1971 (Box 3)
    - Sabbatical Leave (Cushman), 1966-1978 (Box 3)
    - Smith, H. Shelton, 1977-1978 (Box 3)
    - Smith, H. Shelton - Divinity School Changes Name, 1977 (Box 3)
    - Students - Correspondence, 1949-1957 (Box 3)
    - Students - Correspondence, 1959-1966 (Box 3)
    - Students - Correspondence, 1968-1971 (Box 3)
    - Students - Correspondence, 1973-1981 (Box 3)
    - Students - Correspondence, 1982-1986 (Box 3)
    - Students - Correspondence, 1962 (Box 3)
    - Summer School, 1964 (Box 3)
    - S, 1961-1965 (Box 3)
    - Summer School, 1965 (Box 3)
    - Summer Inquiries, 1966 (Box 3)
    - T, 1960-1965 (Box 3)
    - Teaching - Cassette Tapes, 1962 (Box 3)
    - U, 1963 (Box 3)
    - V, 1963-1964 (Box 3)
    - W, 1958-1964 (Box 3)
    - Walton, A. J., 1949-1956 (Box 3)
    - Walton, A. J., 1951-1955 (Box 3)
    - XYZ, 1959-1965 (Box 3)
  - Divinity School Committees and Operations, 1952-1984, undated; 3
    Contains minutes and agendas from committee meetings; faculty and student bulletins; materials about internal business such as admissions, syllabi, and chapel convocations. There are also materials on a major review of the Divinity School curriculum conducted in the late 1960s. A number of addresses to Divinity School students (opening convocations) as well as course lectures can be found in Series 3: Writings. Information about the divinity school self-study can be found in Student Dissent subseries. The subseries is arranged alphabetically by subject.
    - Academic Standing Committee, 1971 (Box 4)
    - Academic Standing Committee, 1959-1963 (Box 4)
    - Administration and Public Affairs, 1968-1973 (Box 4)
    - Admissions Committee, 1958-1965 (Box 4)
    - Admissions and Recruitment, 1968-1969 (Box 4)
    - American Management Association - Operation Dialogue, 1964-1967 (Box 4)
    - Approved Supply Pastor's School, 1952-1962 (Box 4)
    - Divinity School Bequests, 1958-1962 (Box 4)
    - Black Studies, 1969 (Box 4)
    - Board of Visitors, 1969 (Box 4)
    - Black Manifesto, 1969 (Box 4)
    - Budgeting, 1965-1966 (Box 4)
      Restricted until 2036
    - Christian Convocation, 1959-1962 (Box 4)
    - College Sustaining Fund, 1960-1962 (Box 4)
    - Chapel Worship Committee, 1960-1969 (Box 4)
    - Christian Responsibilty and Cultural Trends Committee, 1960-1967 (Box 4)
    - Community Life Committee, 1958-1964 (Box 4)
    - Continuing Education for Ministers, 1960-1971 (Box 4)
    - Continuing Education Seminar - The Bible in the Parish, 1981 (Box 4)
    - Convocation, 1959-1971 (Box 4)
    - Course Enrollment Memos, 1981-1982 (Box 4)
    - Course Examinations, 1973-1985 (Box 4)
    - Course Syllabi, 1960-1978 (Box 4)
    - Course Syllabi, 1955-1958 (Box 4)
    - Course Syllabi, 1974-1980 (Box 4)
    - Course Syllabi, 1982 (Box 4)
    - Course Syllabi, 1982 (Box 4)
    - Curriculum Committee: Committee for Continuing Study of Curriculum, 1967-1969 (Box 4)
    - Curriculum Committee: Committee for Continuing Study of Curriculum, 1967-1969 (Box 4)
    - Curriculum Committee, 1965-1966 (Box 4)
    - Curriculum Committee, 1965-1969 (Box 4)
    - Curriculum Committee, 1960-1964 (Box 4)
    - Curriculum Committee: Report to Graduate Faculty in Religion, 1963, 1968 (Box 4)
    - Curriculum Committee: Jarvis Report, 1962 (Box 4)
    - Curriculum Committee: Jarvis Report I - Biblical Studies, undated (Box 4)
    - Curriculum Committee: Jarvis Report I - Historical Studies, undated (Box 4)
    - Curriculum Committee: Jarvis Report I - Theological Studies, undated (Box 5)
    - Curriculum Committee: Jarvis Report I - Professional Studies, undated (Box 5)
    - Curriculum Committee: Jarvis Report I - General Comments, 1962 (Box 5)
    - Curriculum Committee: Jarvis Report II - Biblical Studies, undated (Box 5)
    - Curriculum Committee: Jarvis Report II - Historical Studies, undated (Box 5)
    - Curriculum Committee: Jarvis Report II - Theological Studies, undated (Box 5)
    - Curriculum Committee: Jarvis Report II - Professional Studies, 1962 (Box 5)
    - Curriculum Committee: Jarvis Report II - Addendum (C.H. 40), undated (Box 5)
    - Curriculum Committee: Jarvis Report II - Vocational Groups, undated (Box 5)
    - Dean Selection Committee, 1970-1971 (Box 5)
    - Dean's Report to the President, 1966-1967 (Box 5)
    - Dean's Report to the President, 1967-1968 (Box 5)
    - Dean's Report to the President, 1970 (Box 5)
    - Degree Nomenclature Committee, 1966 (Box 5)
    - Duke Divinity School Bulletin: Post Office Fund, 1961-1962 (Box 5)
    - Divinity School Calendar, 1965-1966 (Box 5)
    - Divinity School Chapel, 1982 (Box 5)
    - Divinity School Enrollment, 1958-1969 (Box 5)
      Restricted until 2039
    - Entrance Porch Dedication, 1965 (Box 5)
    - Divinity School Expansion: Capital Expansion - Edens, 1958-1959 (Box 5)
    - Divinity School Expansion: Suggestions, 1960-1968 (Box 5)
    - Divinity School Expansion: Photos - Architect's Designs, [1966?] (Box 5)
    - Divinity School Expansion: Blueprint (Oversize-folder 1)
    - Divinity School Expansion, 1966 (Box 5)
    - Divinity School Expansion, 1966 (Box 5)
    - Editorial Committee Report: Divinity School Review, 1962-1968 (Box 5)
    - Divinity School Seminars, 1959-1969 (Box 5)
    - Divinity School Seminars, 1960-1965 (Box 5)
    - Educational Affairs Council, 1969-1970 (Box 5)
    - Educational Affairs Council, 1970-1971 (Box 5)
    - Educational Goals Committee, 1964 (Box 5)
    - Faculty Bulletin vol. I, 1958-1959 (Box 5)
    - Faculty Bulletin vol. II, 1959-1960 (Box 5)
    - Faculty Bulletin vol. III, 1960-1961 (Box 5)
    - Faculty Bulletin vol. IV, 1961-1962 (Box 5)
    - Faculty Bulletin vol. V, 1962-1963 (Box 5)
    - Faculty Bulletin vol. VI, 1963-1964 (Box 5)
    - Faculty Bulletin vol. VII, 1964-1965 (Box 5)
    - Faculty Bulletin vol. VIII, 1965-1966 (Box 5)
    - Faculty Bulletins, 1966-1967 (Box 5)
    - Faculty Bulletin, 1967-1968 (Box 5)
    - Faculty Bulletin, 1968-1969 (Box 5)
    - Faculty Bulletin, 1969-1970 (Box 5)
    - Faculty Bulletins vo. XIII, 1970-1971 (Box 5)
    - Divinity School Fall Seminar, 1978 (Box 6)
    - Faculty Committee Reports, 1969 (Box 6)
    - Faculty Executive Council, 1968-1970 (Box 6)
    - Faculty Executive Council, 1970-1971 (Box 6)
    - Faculty Executive Council, 1970 (Box 6)
    - Faculty Executive Council: Special Meeting, 1969-1970 (Box 6)
    - Faculty Minutes et al., 1975-1978 (Box 6)
    - Field Education, 1970 (Box 6)
    - Field Education, 1970-1971 (Box 6)
    - Field Education Committee, 1966-1967 (Box 6)
    - Graduate Program, 1961-1971 (Box 6)
    - Graduate Program: Formation of Executive Council, 1960-1963 (Box 6)
    - Graduate Division - Official Business, 1958-1971 (Box 6)
    - Graduate School: Th. M. Degree Program, 1967 (Box 6)
    - Graduate Students, 1969 Fall (Box 6)
    - Graduates of Doctoral Program, 1978-1981 (Box 6)
    - Graduate Procedures, 1957-1960 (Box 6)
    - Grants: Statement of Intent, 1966 (Box 6)
    - Hock Memorial Fund, 1961 (Box 6)
    - Lectures and Public Events Committee, 1958-1967 (Box 6)
    - Long Range Planning in Religion Report, 1961 (Box 6)
    - Married Students Statistics, 1960 (Box 6)
    - Ministerial Image Conference, 1965 May 8 (Box 6)
    - Ministerial Student Exemption Form, undated (Box 6)
    - Ministering-in-Context, 1970 (Box 6)
    - Ministerial and Professional Qualification Committee, 1968 (Box 6)
    - Committee to Study the Ministry (Hyde and Esch), 1970 (Box 6)
    - North Carolina Cabinet Conferences, 1959 (Box 6)
    - Official Events, 1974 (Box 6)
    - Organizational Restructuring of Divinity School: Related Documents, 1968-1969 (Box 6)
    - Ormond Center for Planning, Research, and Development, 1980 (Box 6)
    - Planning and Development in the Department of Religion Committee, 1958 (Box 6)
    - Professional Doctorate of the Ministry Preliminary Studies, 1971 (Box 6)
    - Policy and Appointments Committee, 1966-1968 (Box 6)
    - Prayers, 1984 (Box 6)
    - Recruitment Committee (MATS), 1961-1962 (Box 6)
    - Research Grant Monies, 1975-1979 (Box 6)
    - Rudin, John, 1961-1969 (Box 6)
    - Rudin, John, 1961-1966 (Box 6)
    - Rudin, John, 1969 (Box 6)
    - Scholarships and Financial Aid, 1965-1971 (Box 6)
    - Scholarships: Cleland Scholarship, 1961-1963 (Box 6)
    - Scholarships: Scholarship Committee, 1959-1965 (Box 6)
    - Scholarships: Miscellaneous Scholarships, 1960-1962 (Box 6)
    - Scholarships: Divinity School Fund-Choir, 1962 (Box 7)
    - Scholarship Statements: Funds and Figures, 1960 (Box 7)
    - Scholarships: Merit Scholarships, 1965-1966 (Box 7)
    - South Carolina Conference Sustaining Fund, 1960 (Box 7)
    - Social Concerns, 1969 (Box 7)
    - Student Admissions Study, 1970 (Box 7)
    - Student Association, 1970-1971 (Box 7)
    - Student Association Response to Self-Study, 1969-1970 (Box 7)
    - Student Bulletin vol. VI, 1963-1964 (Box 7)
    - Student Bulletin vol. VII, 1964-1965 (Box 7)
    - Student Bulletin vol. VIII, 1965-1966 (Box 7)
    - Student Bulletin vol. IX and vol. X, 1966, 1968 (Box 7)
    - Student Bulletin, 1969-1970 (Box 7)
    - Student Bulletin vol. XIII, 1970-1971 (Box 7)
    - Student Life and Professional Qualifications Committee, 1959-1963 (Box 7)
    - Student Records, 1964-1965 (Box 7)
    - Student Rosters, 1980-1981 (Box 7)
    - Student Rosters, 1983-1984 (Box 7)
    - Taxes Memorandum, 1961 (Box 7)
    - Traffic Regulations, 1960-1964 (Box 7)
    - Typing Bureau: Statistics, Syllabi, etc. costs, 1961-1964 (Box 7)
    - Undergraduate Faculty Council, 1964 (Box 7)
    - University Admissions Committee, 1962 (Box 7)
    - University Calendar Reconsideration, 1963-1964 (Box 7)
    - University Development Program, 1958 (Box 7)
    - University Development Program, 1958 (Box 7)
    - University Leaflets and Reports, 1958-1959, 1970 (Box 7)
    - University Leaflets and Reports, 1969-1970 (Box 7)
    - University Miscellaneous Matters, 1969 (Box 7)
    - University Planning Committee, 1962 (Box 7)
  - Student Dissent, 1953-1983; 4